Hello. Welcome to Sun Life. You're
talking to Martin.
>> We've got a new recruit on the team.
>> Martin Kemp, new face of Sun Life.
Hello.
>> Martin thinks he's in a TV ad.
>> The guaranteed over 50 plan yet is life
insurance. It guarantees the cash payout
for your loved ones when your time
comes. This set is so realistic.
>> You'll be accepted with no medical.
Plus, we guarantee that your premiums
will never rise to you.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we pay out fast, too.
>> What's stupid been in? He's great, isn't
he? Well, thank you for calling.
>> A I just look right down the lens. Cut.
>> There's no pressure. You can choose a
plan that just suits your budget.
>> Okay, de back. You'll also get a welcome
gift card.
>> Can I get one of those?
>> Don't wait. Call or search Sunlife Plan
today and get a free welcome gift card.
Uh,
>> what time do we wrap today?
>> Wrap?